It has begun! The Goo Goo Channel!
Thank you!
This time, we are collaborating with Mr. Tsurioka!
Thank you, Mr. Tsurioka!
I'm Ken!
This is a little old...
It's old, this! Oh no!
This collaboration was quick!
This collaboration was early!
I've been waiting for this! Not yet! Not yet! I was like, "Not yet!
But was it really a month since you did it?
Yeah, like a month.
Oh, my God! Thank you!
So, how was the fishing?
You can actually see some of the fishing
Tsurioka's channel!
Please take a look!
You guys are so good!
Both of them are so good!
We did it! It was my first time!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Hey! That was strong!
She was strong!
You know, it's usually the beginner girls that go down with seasickness.
They get downed!
But, as most people do...
I was worried about her, but she was so strong!
We even managed to catch a fish!
We caught a fish!
A fish!
Can I see it?
See?
It's fun!
I caught the fish myself.
I'll open it!
Riiiight!
Is this it?
You probably caught the biggest one. You probably caught the biggest one.
That's great!
That's it! That's it! That's it!
Big one!
Ta-da!
Congratulations!
Wow!
You got it beautifully!
Have a good fishing!
It was so heavy!
How are you going to eat this today?
This freshly dead fish.
Freshly dead?
We just caught it this morning.
Sashimi for lunch!
Wow! I love it!
Afterwards, we're going to cut up the fish
After that, we're going to cook it for you.
Yes! I'm looking forward to it!
Shall we go to the kitchen?
I'm going to cook!
énerG
Scales first, then the bottom, maybe.
I'll get the scales.
I'll take the scales off, please.
I love scales!
Have you ever cooked a fish before?
No, I've never.
Would you like to try?
Do you cook?
Yes, I cook.
Can you use a knife?
I can hardly use a knife.
I don't.
What is your favorite dish?
Recently, I like sweet potatoes.
I make a lot of sweet potatoes.
I'm a farmer. Farmer did it.
Miso soup.
I took it.
Remove the head.
Is it the same for all fish?
Basically the same.
It's just the structure of the fish is different.
Does it take a lot of effort?
Around here, yes.
But not so much after this.
The fish don't stop.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to cut it into three pieces.
How's the fish?
A special knife for fish.
Do you eat a lot of fish?
I eat a lot of fish.
That's good. It tastes better when you can cut it yourself.
Yes, at home, too.
Yes! That's great!
I'm getting cold feet, Mister. It's all right.
I'm so hungry...
And then I'll remove the ribs.
Very fine.
Now would be good.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Do you usually cook other things?
Oh, I do. Anything.
I have a cooking channel.
What about specialties?
Singular cuisine is synthetic clothing food.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You want to do this?
I'm going to take the innards here.
Yes, sir.
I asked you to do it for me because my back was hurting.
Okay, Ai, let's go.
How can I help you? What should I do?
You cut here, and then you cut here.
Then you cut here, and then you cut here, and then you cut here, and then you cut here.
Do you go all the way down?
It takes a lot of strength to cut the skin.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's hard.
It's harder than you think.
Oh, no.
It's a little wobbly down there.
Thank you very much.
I'm starving.
It's not good, is it?
Is it cut?
Yes, it is.
You put a lot of effort into it.
Even housewives who are good cooks can't cut fish.
Is this enough?
It's all right. It's all right. Good!
Are there fish with soft skin?
No, mostly big fish are hard to cut like this.
There are different knives and different parts of the knife to use.
Which part do you recommend?
Put it on the belly and pull this side.
Great!
I have a knack for fish.
You have to use the root from the tip.
Sorry, I did that.
It went so fast!
The next one is the hardest.
This one's called skinning.
This is the hardest part.
Just pull the skin off.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, no! I missed!
Aah!
It's so hard!
I'm sorry I missed!Sorry for the miss!
I'm in the middle of something and it's hard to pull from this.
Difficulty level up!
I'm sorry I decided to increase the difficulty.
Okay.
Turn it up a little bit.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Yes! - Oh, my gosh! That's good!
OK!
Oh! That's great!
It looks like this!
Beautiful!
Next, make it into sashimi!
Sashimi like this!
The thickness is good!
Finally, we put it up for some reason, it looks better like this!
Try it one way or the other!
I can't do it!
What's the trick?
Pulling!
This one cuts when you pull from the back!
So don't push, pull!
Be careful!
Keep pulling and pulling!
Good! Good! Very good!
If you don't get it right the first time, you can go back one more time.
If you go a little further, you can hold the knife up and give it a final slice!
Oh, isn't that good?
It's sticking!
It's sticking a little bit!
Ah! Oh!
Nice!
This is so hard!
You can be a sushi chef now!
Can I be a sushi chef now?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you ready?
I'm nervous!
With so many adults watching us!
Pulling all the way from the base!
Is this about right?
Yes!
No squeaking!
What! Straight? Straight?
Straight! It's like pulling to cut!
Very good! Very good!
Stand up at the end. That's what I mean!
You're so good! Genius!
Talent!
I got it!
Very good! Really, really good!
It's actually better when it's aged.
It's better to let it sit for a few days before eating.
But some people prefer it freshly caught.
So you can eat aged fish anywhere, anytime.
but you can't eat this kind of freshly caught fish.
You can't eat this kind of freshly caught fish.
You can't get it in a restaurant!
The texture!
It's so soft and chewy!
What? !
Yellowtail doesn't have that image?
Yes! Any fish can be soft and chewy!
I wanted to fish three hours ago!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I stopped you! I held it back!
That was beautiful.
Nice fight!
You fought!
I thought you were gonna fall in the ocean.
No, I thought I was going to fall in, too.
Do you fish in the first place? Do you fish?
Fishing, is this your first time?
Atan, I used to work at a sushi restaurant.
Really?
That's a lie.
A lie?
A lie.
The color, the red guy.
It was a bright red lie.
Redder than me.
Red and green, right?
Yes, Christmas colors.
I like it.
It's done!
Looks delicious!
Beautiful!
Delicious!
So beautiful!
Actually, the captain caught it on that boat.
This is an anglerfish.
It's a very expensive fish.
You don't get many chances to eat it as sashimi.
While everyone else is eating it, I'm going to cut it up.
The captain
I rarely have a chance to eat fresh sashimi.
I'll process it for you.
Thank you very much.
(background music)
Wow! So many!
So many!
It's so extravagant!
Oh, no!
I'm going to eat it!
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious!
Let's both try it first. Try it for two first.
Delicious!
Delicious! It's so soft and juicy!
I don't think I've ever tasted anything like it.
It's so sweet!
Yummy!
Mmm! Yummy!
Yum!
It's sweet, really sweet.
Very spicy.
May I? Eat it.
Bon appétit!
It's so chewy!
Delicious!
It's been a while since I ate a freshly caught one, so yummy!
Call it a bluefin squid in the spring.
It's really
It's cooler
It doesn't swing offshore like it does today.
That's why it's so good
Eh!
You can catch them
Freshly caught
Anglers' Choice
The No. 1 fish on the list of the best fish to catch
horse mackerel.
So it's surprising that
Sushi local
You can go to a sushi restaurant
than the popular fish at the supermarket.
From an angler's point of view
Squid and horse mackerel are the best freshly caught fish
Squid is the clear Cuttlefish are transparent.
I eat a lot of squid.
I really do.
Squid in a bucket.
Bring it back.
And then we'll take the live ones and bam! Boom!
and they're so clear and so delicious.
I wish you could eat it.
Spring, fisherman.
See you later.
Call me Sakura, next time.
Shime!
Oh my god, you're my favorite!
You guessed them all.
It's called a "box of guesses".
Boxes of guesses.
Wow!
It's a Niogigi Mussel!
Nioggia.
It's like a manatee.
Let's bake persimmons!
It's huge! Oysters like this!
In the good place of your choice!
People who want to bake often come in.
Yes, sir!
So cute!
All right.
I cut it out.
A big one.
It tastes so juicy!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
If this tastes good
Delicious!
The next delicious one
Little chestnuts on one side
Irresistible spiciness
Oh, it's delicious! Oh, that's delicious.
Thank you so much.
Mmm! Is it good?
It's good, right?
I love it!
Mmm! It's so good!
I'm so happy!
Oh, yum!
Saogashira's dad caught this for the captain today.
He caught a lot of fish.
I'm so happy for him!
Even for a beginner fisherman, it's easy to do.
I think you taught me how to do it.
It's surprisingly easy, isn't it?
Don't you ever get tired of fishing? Fishing?
No?
No.
I've been doing it alone on Nico Nico Douga for a long time.
And then we became a couple.
I've been doing it for about 6 years?
Then I quit and it's been about 2 years.
I think YouTube is very popular these days.
So when I said, "Let's do YouTube.
I thought I'd choose a genre that wasn't on YouTube.
There were only about two YouTubers who were into fishing.
I said, "Okay, let's do fishing.
I didn't have any experience at that time.
You did fishing when you were on Nico Nico Nico?
I was doing something else, like live streaming.
That kind of thing.
So, like, a good pro, you know?
Someone good-looking.
But not amateurs.
So I decided to make a video about a family where beginners can become good at it.
That's interesting.
Are there many of them now? Fishing.
Fishing is really popular now.
I think there are a lot of people. That's a lot, isn't it?
Over a thousand couples, I'd say.
That's great.
Was it really that small?
I think it was 2015.
Eight years ago, there were only a couple of couples.
YouTubers weren't even a household word yet.
So I thought I'd take advantage of it.
How long have you been doing this, by the way?
Since 2015.
That's the same time!
We're in the same boat.
We're in the same class.
Eight years ago, right?
Eight years ago, we were already...
We had a hard time? First of all
It was tough. I hardly slept.
Editing and stuff.
You did that all by yourselves?
I did it all myself.
I was doing it all by myself.
I had a little bit of help from a few people.
After six months or a year
Then, after a year, the three of us started working together.
And then the number of people started to increase.
Now we have about 30 employees.
There was a period of time when it was just the three of us, about two years.
It was tough.
I was so stressed.
When I sat down at the computer
I'd sit in front of the computer, and I'd get a bar of timbacin.
I didn't have time to sleep anymore.
So when I had to go home, I saved my money and grabbed the freeway
down the road.
It's tough.
And there's nothing to eat.
A little bit of food
Grow some veggies. Grow vegetables.
Eat wild grass for a living.
Or just yakisoba noodles.
Super convenient
Just yakisoba noodles without any ingredients
Luxury
Selling yakisoba noodles is better
If you catch one, eat it
If you catch one...
I'll say, "Yay, I'm a winner today!
We spent 100 yen for each hamburger.
Even 300 yen was extravagant.
At first, the three of us lived together.
In Saga?
Saga.
Do you still live together?
We've only recently broken up.
It's been about 7 years.
You haven't had any fights?
No, not really.
I'm calling for death.
We're just a bunch of old guys.
We're probably the oldest YouTubers in the world.
How old are you?
I was like 25 when I started Nico Nico Douga.
I was like 25 or something.
I'm going to be 40 years old by the time I'm active.
The average age is going down.
That's right.
This is mine.
Oh, right.
Oh, please, please, please, please.
Okay, it's coming, it's coming
Oh, yeah. Usuka.
We'll take all of it. We'll go in.
Oh, oh
The average age of the population has dropped.
Tsubu hill theme song to be written? Tsubu hill theme song to be written?
Yes, really.
We'll sing it together at the festival.
I'm so afraid.
I'd like to have an artist from the saga to write the opening song.
I've been using the opening song for 5 or 6 years now.
We've been using it for 5 or 6 years now.
to a big girl.
Oh, the manager nodding his head
I'm so proud of you.
For inviting us to Fukuoka Park.
Really?
They invited us.
Yay!
After the show, we're gonna get squidgy.
We did it. We really did it.
You can just go.
After the show.
Hand it out to the audience.
Throw them at the audience
Next year, we'll fish for squid.
I promise you.
But first...
One more thing.
I want you to come to the summer festival
Before that we will have our live
Live fishing festival
And maybe some flounder.
I know you have Spanish mackerel
Hiramasa, yellowtail.
Eh, looks delicious
Looks long!
Tuna with long arms.
Tuna with long arms!
And...
Do you fish?
I've never fished before. First time.
First time.
I don't know how to use it
I don't know.
How about a boat stop?
I've never done it before.
I might.
I don't know.
ED.
They're leaving.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's so comfortable!
It's fun.
You're still going strong, aren't you?
We'll see.
It's going to take me about half an hour.
That's true.
Let's go for it.
What's this?
Yohechon.
It's a yo-ho-chon.
How much longer till we get there?
I'll take care of it.
Five minutes.
Five more minutes?
Five more minutes, they say.
Almost there.
Almost there?
It won't be long now.
You want to wait for 30 minutes?
Wait?
I could wait.
About ten minutes.
I'll be there at 6:00.
That's good. That's good.
Doesn't time seem to fly by when you're moving so fast?
Yes, it does.Yeah.
Not really.
The Theory of Relativity
Yes, ma'am.
It's 2:30.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
He's really starting to fly.
I'm so surprised. Is he going to do most of it?
I was so surprised.
Yohen!
How much time left?
Four more...
Four minutes!
Almost there! Four more minutes!
Ah...
You know, you see war movies sometimes.
I'm Jin's assistant.
In the passenger seat
There's a fish.
Hold it with your thumb and drop it slowly.
Drop it 50 meters.
Click it again.
Turn it around and click it back in.
Then raise it to 30 meters.
Repeat this process to catch the small fish.
Once the small fish are attached
Drop down to the bottom and leave it this time.
Let's try it again.
Oh, there it goes.
Click again and repeat.
That's interesting.
Click and repeat.
Just stop this.
I can wind this up a little bit at a time. This one can be rolled up a little at a time.
This one can be rolled automatically.
I can hold it a little bit at a time.
And then you can ask the fish to come up to about 30 meters.
Wait for the little fish to come to you.
Oh!
Ooh.
oh?
Oh!
Ooh.
He's not here yet.
No, they're not here.
Not yet.
There are so many schools of small fish.
When there's a lot of fish, they don't react well.
But with this, we can catch fish.
Then, one of the fish in the school got caught.
And one of the fish in the school got caught.
And the big one will be like...
It's like he has to eat.
It's like he's instinctively backing up.
Like he's got to eat?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's why even if there are a lot of sardines
Aim for the sardines on the hook.
That's when they go berserk.
I see.
That's right, that's right
Thanks to that, still,
And what about the small fish like,
Let's start a little higher up again.
Who was Kim, who was she, who was she drunk with? We met the other night.
That's the girl, isn't it?
Little camaraderie.
Little camaraderie?
Little kama'ai. Kama'i-chan
Cama'ai, my guess.
No, you're a Pitstan guess.
You mean you're a "box person"?
Boxed guesses.
I have a girl. I know her name.
She was here the other day.
She has the best voice.
The girl in the morning. The girl in the morning.
I wasn't interested in idols or anything like that.
Um, they're cute, all of them.
I could see why you'd want to support them.
Still nice.
It's close.
Did you catch it?
I've got one! It's working!
Oh, my God!
It's working! We're catching them!
It's great!
Oh, my God!
It's already eating!
It's pushing!
It's coming! It's coming!
Is it coming?
Shall I turn it by hand?
Like this?
Slowly! Slowly!
Slowly! Slowly! Slowly!
Oh, my God! That's great!
Yes!
That's great!
Ah! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Just snap the bottom!
Lever! Lever!
Lever up!
Oh, my God! It's heavy! It's heavy! It's amazing! Heavy! It's heavy!
It's heavy!
But if you use electric power, you'll be fine.
Balls!
Oh, my gosh!
Come on!
Oh, my God! This is huge!
Oh, it looks so big, it's normal.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Thanks, Dad.
Is he lucky?
I'm lucky, I'm lucky, I'm lucky.
Are you lucky?
I'm good. I'm good!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on up and wait.
Come up and wait
Come on, come on, come on
Just like your father
Wow!
That's a big one.
Maybe there's two of them.
Maybe he's got two of them.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Your student is bigger.
He's very good, sir.
He's got a good fight, too.
Let's wind it up on the way up.
I'm winding it up.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
How many more meters?How many meters?
Nine more meters.
Nine more meters!
Slowly, by hand.
Start hand-winding at five meters.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Last ditch effort.
Come on, come on, come on
Till you see the yellow ball
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
This one's big, isn't it?
Oh!
Surf right, please.
That's it.
Roll it, roll it, roll it.
I see it. I see it.
Almost there.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Stup.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah!
Wow.
Yay!
Wasshoi wasshoi
Wasshoi wasshoi wasshoi
Bang-chang bang-chang!
That's great!
It's so big!
Nice!
Big, big, big.
Oh, wow.
Very big.
Nice.
Nice. Nice.
Almost there.
It's so big!
It's big.
This is the house.
Yellowtail.
Yellowtail?
I've never caught a yellowtail before.
Nice.
My first yellowtail!
Oh, man!
It was so heavy!
Wow!
It's so heavy!
It's heavy.
Wow.
No, no, no.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
You've been eating Face.
Oh, my God.
It was so heavy.
Fishing is fun, isn't it?
Fishing must be fun.
And a bath.
Don't mind me.
So, thank you for this collaboration, Tsuri-oka-san!
Thank you very much!
How was it?
It was fun! It was Hajime-chan's favorite.
She taught me very kindly.
Next time, he'll be stricter.
The fish were delicious.
You mean you can catch and eat them right away like this?
How is it?
I mean, last time I was on a talk show, they were all better than us. That's what I was saying, last time I was on a talk show, everyone was more solid than we were.
I thought it was because our power was so small that we decided to collaborate with you.
Thank you very much.
It's tough when you go fishing for the first time.
You worked hard during the fishing trip.
And the seasickness, you know, you got down once, but you did it one more time.
I really wanted to cheer you up.
You didn't look like you were having a hard time today.
Yes! You look great for such a young guy.
I'm rooting for you!
Thank you!
Please come to the show!
Please come!
And the yellow one.
What yellow! It's purple!
Oh! Purple!
I'm screwed!
Sorry, red and green, green and blue.
But also a little bit more, live more.
A little more sparkle.
No, it's still nice!
Really? I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
I'll try to do a little more from now on.
Next time, we'll go fishing for squid.
Yes, of course! Yes! I'd love to!
I'd love to go!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!